https://www.lukabloom.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
MY ACCOUNT | BASKET | CHECKOUT
Terms, Conditions & PoliciesData Privacy and Website CookiesWe use cookies to collect anonymous personal data from website visitors in order to track marketing efforts.If you register or purchase a product, the site collects personal data including name, IP, address and email address in order to process your transaction.We use PayPal, a reputable third party secure payment service to collect the payment data and process the payment on behalf of LukaBloom.com (see www.paypal.com for more information on their data collection and privacy statement).We do not share customer data that we collect with any other third party.Email Marketing PolicyWe dislike email spam just as much as you do. Our email lists is ‘opt-in’ and LukaBloom.com emails always includes an unsubscribe option on all marketing emails.Delivery and Returns PolicyShipping charges: free shipping on all items, worldwide.Physical goods (CDs, books, etc) will be delivered within 30 days, usually much quicker than this – typically less than a week.Online goods (digital music, etc) are available online immediately after purchase. Music is normally supplied in mp3 format unless stated otherwise on the product page.In the event of defects in the original product or where products are not delivered to you due to a mistake on our part, we will send the item to you again without extra charge. There will not be a further shipping charge for this exchange.For obvious reasons, digital downloads are not returnable or refundable.This does not affect your statutory rights.Contact InfoIf you have a query about an order, contact Anne at orders@lukabloom.comOur AddressSureflameKnockliscraneMiltown MalbayCo. ClareIrelandWho we areOur website address is: https://www.lukabloom.com.What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact formsCookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.How long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
STORIES
FACEBOOK
NEWSLETTER
BOOKINGS
PRESS
Menu
STORIES
FACEBOOK
All Rights Reserved - Luka Bloom. Cookies Notice & Privacy Policy. Website by WebsiteDoctor.
